

Contact

Phone:

+48 889 549 270

Email:

agatalipiak25@gmail.com

Languages

English – B2

German - A1

Hobbies

Culinary

Brewing

Football

Martial Arts

Movies

Fitness

Agata Lipiak

About me

I am 27 years old and since last year I have been intensively learning programming in JavaScript in order to get a job as a Front-end Developer. I am a very mobilized person who achieves his goals, which is why I have successfully completed so many projects in my current job. Programming has become my passion and I would like to develop my skills in this direction.

Skills

- React, Redux, Styled Components
- JavaScript, ES6+
- GitHub
- CSS3
- HTML5
- SASS

- Node.js and PostgreSQL
- Interpersonal skills
- Team work
- Work planning and organization
- Setting and achieving goals

Projects

I used the knowledge and skills in programming to create the following projects:

My portfolio – a website presenting my programming skills. To create it, I used technologies such as React and Styled Components.

https://www.alipiak.com

Recipe organizer – a website designed for storing, adding and managing recipes. It also allows you to plan recipes for the day and prepare a shopping list. To create it, I used technologies such as React, Redux and Styled Components

https://www.alipiak.com/recipe

Education

Master of Engineering : Mechanical Engineering – 2016 – 2017

Wrocław University of Technology, Faculty of Mechanical Engineering, second-cycle, full-time

Bachelor of Engineering: Material Engineering - 2012 - 2016

Wrocław University of Technology, Faculty of Chemistry, first-cycle, full-time

Experience

Product Engineer - march 2020 - current | STELWELD

Process Engineer – august 2017 – march 2020 | STELWELD